A Guide to the Records of the Virginia Office of Civilian Defense, 1940-1945.
Library of Virginia
- Series I. Correspondence, 1942-1945., Extent: 10.15 cubic feet (29 boxes). (Box 1-29)
  - Correspondence, 1943-1945.
    - Ware, Juliet R. (State Board of Education), 1943-1945. (Box 28, Folder 31)
    - Watkins, George W., Rev. (New Kent County CDC), 1943-1945. (Box 28, Folder 32)
    - Wea-Wey - Miscellaneous, 1943-1945. (Box 28, Folder 33)
    - Webb, H. L. (Greensville County CDC), 1943-1945. (Box 28, Folder 34)
    - Webber, John (War Manpower Commission), 1943-1945. (Box 28, Folder 35)
    - Welton, Courtenay S. (War Production Board), 1943-1945. (Box 28, Folder 36)
    - West, R. John, Col. (Lynchburg CDC), 1943-1945. (Box 28, Folder 37)
    - Wha-Who - Miscellaneous, 1943-1945. (Box 28, Folder 38)
    - White, B. E. (Essex County CDC), 1943-1945. (Box 28, Folder 39)
    - White, E. L., Col. (U.S. Office of Civilian Defense - Protective Property), 1943-1945. (Box 28, Folder 40)
    - White, Herman (South Norfolk CDC), 1943-1945. (Box 28, Folder 41)
    - White, Edna Holmes (King and Queen County), 1943-1945. (Box 28, Folder 42)
    - White, J. Stuart (War Finance Committee for Virginia), 1943-1945. (Box 28, Folder 43)
    - Whitehead, Henry C. (Norfolk CDC), 1943-1945. (Box 28, Folder 44)
    - Whitesell, S. M. (Fries CDC), 1943-1945. (Box 28, Folder 45)
    - Wic-Wit - Miscellaneous, 1943-1945. (Box 28, Folder 46)
    - Wilcox, Jerome (University of California Berkeley Library), 1943-1945. (Box 29, Folder 1)
    - Wiley, Ethel (Nelson County), 1943-1945. (Box 29, Folder 2)
    - Will, J. E. (Page County CDC), 1943-1945. (Box 29, Folder 3)
    - Wilkinson, J. S. (Burkeville CDC), 1943-1945. (Box 29, Folder 4)
    - Williams, Hugh A. (Lexington CDC), 1943-1945. (Box 29, Folder 5)
    - Williams, H. P. (Conserve Critical Resources), 1943-1945. (Box 29, Folder 6)
    - Williams, John D. (Prince William County CDC), 1943-1945. (Box 29, Folder 7)
    - Williams, K. (DuPont Company), 1943-1945. (Box 29, Folder 8)
    - Williams, Lucy (Campbell County CDC), 1943-1945. (Box 29, Folder 9)
    - Williams, Robert F. (State Board of Education), 1943-1945. (Box 29, Folder 10)
    - Williams, W. M. (Rockbridge County CDC), 1943-1945. (Box 29, Folder 11)
    - Willis, Luna (Virginia State Nutrition Committee), 1943-1945. (Box 29, Folder 12)
    - Wills, James S. (Federal Farm Security Administration), 1943-1945. (Box 29, Folder 13)
    - Wilson, C. V. (Lynchburg CDC), 1943-1945. (Box 29, Folder 14)
    - Wilson, L. H. (Crewe CDC), 1943-1945. (Box 29, Folder 15)
    - Winsten, Milton (Petersburg CDC), 1943-1945. (Box 29, Folder 16)
    - Wolfe, J. P., Jr. (Big Stone Gap CDC), 1943-1945. (Box 29, Folder 17)
    - Wood, James H. (Conserve Critical Resources Committee), 1943-1945. (Box 29, Folder 18)
    - Woodbury, M. C., Col. (Norfolk Air Defense), 1943-1945. (Box 29, Folder 19)
    - Woodbury, W. R. (Williamsburg CDC), 1943-1945. (Box 29, Folder 20)
    - Woodcock, Harold F. (Connecticut War Council), 1943-1945. (Box 29, Folder 21)
    - Woodson, C. W., Jr., Maj. (Virginia State Police), 1943-1945. (Box 29, Folder 22)
    - Wol-Wys - Miscellaneous, 1943-1945. (Box 29, Folder 23)
    - Wright, Meredith W. (Amherst County CDC), 1943-1945. (Box 29, Folder 24)
    - Wright, R. D. (Lynchburg Waterworks), 1943-1945. (Box 29, Folder 25)
    - Wright, William A. (Virginia Conservation Commission), 1943-1945. (Box 29, Folder 26)
    - Wyatt, W. Judd (Food Distribution Administration), 1943-1945. (Box 29, Folder 27)
    - Wyse, J. H. (Virginia Office of Civilian Defense), 1943-1945. (Box 29, Folder 28)
    - Y - Miscellaneous, 1943-1945. (Box 29, Folder 29)
    - Yancey, R. C., Jr. (Mecklenburg County CDC), 1943-1945. (Box 29, Folder 30)
    - Yeatts, Coleman B. (Pittsylvania County CDC), 1943-1945. (Box 29, Folder 31)
    - Young, John Russell (Washington Civilian Defense Region), 1943-1945. (Box 29, Folder 32)
    - Z - Miscellaneous, 1943-1945. (Box 29, Folder 33)
    - Zehmer, George B. (UVA Extension Service), 1943-1945. (Box 29, Folder 34)
    - Zeller, Raymond (Third Civilian Defense Region), 1943-1945. (Box 29, Folder 35)
- Series II. Correspondence with localities, 1942-1945., Extent: XX cubic feet (XX boxes). (Box XX)
  This series is housed in XX boxes and is arranged alphabetically by name of locality, with counties, cities and towns being filed together in one sequence. These files consist of incoming correspondence from localities, copies of the outgoing correspondence from the Office of Civilian Defense, and reports. Files were kept separately for 1942 and for 1943-1945 (bulk 1943-1944) and that arrangement is reflected in this series. Most of the copies of outgoing correspondence can also be found in Series I. Correspondence. Outgoing correspondence, 1943-1945, also includes a notation on each letter as to where copies of the letters are also filed in the Subject Files series. The majority of the correspondence is with local civilian defense council (CDC) representatives and locality files are divided into sub-categories for General, Civilian Mobilization, and Civilian Protection.
  - Correspondence with locatilities, 1942.
    - Accomack County
      - General, 1942. (Box 30, Folder 1)
      - General - Publications, 1942. (Box 30, Folder 2)
      - General - Negro activities, 1942. (Box 30, Folder 3)
      - Civilian Mobilization, 1942. (Box 30, Folder 4)
      - Civilian Protection, 1942. (Box 30, Folder 5)
    - Albemarle County
      - General, 1942. (Box 30, Folder 6)
      - Civilian Mobilization, 1942. (Box 30, Folder 7)
      - Civilian Protection, 1942. (Box 30, Folder 8)
    - Alexandria, City of
      - General, 1942. (Box 30, Folder 9)
      - Civilian Mobilization, 1942. (Box 30, Folder 10)
      - Civilian Protection, 1942. (Box 30, Folder 11)
      - Civilian Protection - Federal equipment, 1942. (Box 30, Folder 12)
    - Alleghany County
      - General, 1942. (Box 30, Folder 13)
      - Civilian Protection, 1942. (Box 30, Folder 14)
    - Amelia County
      - General, 1942. (Box 30, Folder 15)
      - Civilian Mobilization, 1942. (Box 30, Folder 16)
      - Civilian Protection, 1942. (Box 30, Folder 17)
    - Amherst County
      - General, 1942. (Box 30, Folder 18)
      - Civilian Mobilization, 1942. (Box 30, Folder 19)
      - Civilian Protection, 1942. (Box 30, Folder 20)
    - Amonate, Town of
      - General, 1942. (Box 30, Folder 21)
    - Appalachia, Town of
      - General, 1942. (Box 30, Folder 22)
      - Civilian Mobilization, 1942. (Box 30, Folder 23)
      - Civilian Protection, 1942. (Box 30, Folder 24)
    - Appomattox County
      - General, 1942. (Box 31, Folder 1)
      - Civilian Mobilization, 1942. (Box 31, Folder 2)
      - Civilian Protection, 1942. (Box 31, Folder 3)
    - Arlington County
      - General, 1942. (Box 31, Folder 4)
      - Civilian Mobilization, 1942. (Box 31, Folder 5)
      - Civilian Protection, 1942. (Box 31, Folder 6)
      - Civilian Protection - Federal equipment, 1942. (Box 31, Folder 7)
    - Augusta County
      - General, 1942. (Box 31, Folder 8)
      - Civilian Mobilization, 1942. (Box 31, Folder 9)
      - Civilian Protection, 1942. (Box 31, Folder 10)
    - Bath County
      - General, 1942. (Box 31, Folder 11)
      - General - Negro activities, 1942. (Box 31, Folder 12)
      - Civilian Mobilization, 1942. (Box 31, Folder 13)
      - Civilian Protection, 1942. (Box 31, Folder 14)
    - Bedford County
      - General, 1942. (Box 31, Folder 15)
      - Civilian Mobilization, 1942. (Box 31, Folder 16)
      - Civilian Protection, 1942. (Box 31, Folder 17)
    - Big Stone Gap, Town of
      - General, 1942. (Box 32, Folder 1)
      - Civilian Mobilization, 1942. (Box 32, Folder 2)
      - Civilian Protection, 1942. (Box 32, Folder 3)
      - Copies to Mr. Wolfe and Ms. Slemp, 1942. (Box 32, Folder 4)
    - Bishop, Town of
      - General, 1942. (Box 32, Folder 5)
    - Blacksburg
      - General, 1942. (Box 32, Folder 6)
      - Civilian Mobilization, 1942. (Box 32, Folder 7)
      - Civilian Protection, 1942. (Box 32, Folder 8)
    - Blackstone, Town of
      - General, 1942. (Box 32, Folder 9)
      - Civilian Protection - Federal equipment, 1942. (Box 32, Folder 10)
    - Bland County
      - General, 1942. (Box 32, Folder 11)
      - Civilian Mobilization, 1942. (Box 32, Folder 12)
      - Civilian Protection, 1942. (Box 32, Folder 13)
    - Bluefield, Town of
      - General, 1942. (Box 32, Folder 14)
      - Civilian Mobilization, 1942. (Box 32, Folder 15)
    - Botetourt County
      - General, 1942. (Box 32, Folder 16)
      - Civilian Mobilization, 1942. (Box 32, Folder 17)
      - Civilian Protection, 1942. (Box 32, Folder 18)
    - Bristol
      - General, 1942. (Box 32, Folder 19)
      - Civilian Mobilization, 1942. (Box 32, Folder 20)
      - Civilian Protection, 1942. (Box 33, Folder 1)
      - T. B. Shelburne, 1942. (Box 33, Folder 2)
    - Brunswick County
      - General, 1942. (Box 33, Folder 3)
      - Civilian Mobilization, 1942. (Box 33, Folder 4)
      - Civilian Protection, 1942. (Box 33, Folder 5)
    - Buchanan County
      - General, 1942. (Box 33, Folder 6)
      - Civilian Mobilization, 1942. (Box 33, Folder 7)
      - Civilian Protection, 1942. (Box 33, Folder 8)
    - Buckingham County
      - General, 1942. (Box 33, Folder 9)
      - Civilian Mobilization, 1942. (Box 33, Folder 10)
      - Civilian Protection, 1942. (Box 33, Folder 11)
    - Buena Vista
      - General, 1942. (Box 33, Folder 12)
      - Civilian Mobilization, 1942. (Box 33, Folder 13)
      - Civilian Protection, 1942. (Box 33, Folder 14)
    - Burkeville, Town of
      - General, 1942. (Box 33, Folder 15)
    - Campbell County
      - General, 1942. (Box 33, Folder 16)
      - Civilian Mobilization, 1942. (Box 33, Folder 17)
      - Civilian Protection, 1942. (Box 33, Folder 18)
    - Cape Charles (town of)
      - General, 1942. (Box 34, Folder 1)
      - Civilian Mobilization, 1942. (Box 34, Folder 2)
      - Civilian Protection, 1942. (Box 34, Folder 3)
    - Caroline County
      - General, 1942. (Box 34, Folder 4)
      - General - Negro activities, 1942. (Box 34, Folder 5)
      - Civilian Mobilization, 1942. (Box 34, Folder 6)
      - Civilian Protection, 1942. (Box 34, Folder 7)
    - Carroll County
      - General, 1942. (Box 34, Folder 8)
      - Civilian Mobilization, 1942. (Box 34, Folder 9)
      - Civilian Protection, 1942. (Box 34, Folder 10)
    - Charles City County
      - General, 1942. (Box 34, Folder 11)
      - Civilian Mobilization, 1942. (Box 34, Folder 12)
      - Civilian Protection, 1942. (Box 34, Folder 13)
    - Charlotte County
      - General, 1942. (Box 34, Folder 14)
      - Civilian Mobilization, 1942. (Box 34, Folder 15)
      - Civilian Protection, 1942. (Box 34, Folder 16)
    - Charlottesville
      - General, 1942. (Box 34, Folder 17)
      - General - Negro activities, 1942. (Box 34, Folder 18)
      - Civilian Mobilization, 1942. (Box 34, Folder 19)
      - Civilian Protection, 1942. (Box 34, Folder 20)
    - Chesterfield County
      - General, 1942. (Box 35, Folder 1)
      - Civilian Mobilization, 1942. (Box 35, Folder 2)
      - Civilian Protection, 1942. (Box 35, Folder 3)
    - Christiansburg (town of)
      - General, 1942. (Box 35, Folder 4)
      - Civilian Mobilization, 1942. (Box 35, Folder 5)
      - Civilian Protection, 1942. (Box 35, Folder 6)
    - Clarke County
      - General, 1942. (Box 35, Folder 7)
      - Civilian Mobilization, 1942. (Box 35, Folder 8)
      - Civilian Protection, 1942. (Box 35, Folder 9)
    - Clifton Forge
      - General, 1942. (Box 35, Folder 10)
      - Civilian Mobilization, 1942. (Box 35, Folder 11)
      - Civilian Protection, 1942. (Box 35, Folder 12)
    - Colonial Heights (town of)
      - General, 1942. (Box 35, Folder 13)
      - Civilian Mobilization, 1942. (Box 35, Folder 14)
      - Civilian Protection, 1942. (Box 35, Folder 15)
    - Covington
      - General, 1942. (Box 35, Folder 16)
      - Civilian Mobilization, 1942. (Box 35, Folder 17)
      - Civilian Protection, 1942. (Box 35, Folder 18)
    - Craig County
      - General, 1942. (Box 35, Folder 19)
    - Crewe (town of)
      - General, 1942. (Box 35, Folder 20)
    - Culpeper County
      - General, 1942. (Box 36, Folder 1)
      - Civilian Mobilization, 1942. (Box 36, Folder 2)
      - Civilian Protection, 1942. (Box 36, Folder 3)
    - Cumberland County
      - General, 1942. (Box 36, Folder 4)
      - Civilian Mobilization, 1942. (Box 36, Folder 5)
      - Civilian Protection, 1942. (Box 36, Folder 6)
    - Danville
      - General, 1942. (Box 36, Folder 7)
      - Civilian Mobilization, 1942. (Box 36, Folder 8)
      - Civilian Protection, 1942. (Box 36, Folder 9)
      - Civilian Protection - Federal equipment, 1942. (Box 36, Folder 10)
    - Dendron (town of)
      - General, 1942. (Box 37, Folder 1)
    - Dickenson County
      - General, 1942. (Box 37, Folder 2)
      - Civilian Mobilization, 1942. (Box 37, Folder 3)
      - Civilian Protection, 1942. (Box 37, Folder 4)
    - Dinwiddie County
      - General, 1942. (Box 37, Folder 5)
      - Civilian Mobilization, 1942. (Box 37, Folder 6)
      - Civilian Protection, 1942. (Box 37, Folder 7)
    - Elizabeth City County
      - General, 1942. (Box 37, Folder 8)
      - Civilian Mobilization, 1942. (Box 37, Folder 9)
      - Civilian Protection, 1942. (Box 37, Folder 10)
      - Civilian Protection - Federal equipment, 1942. (Box 37, Folder 11)
    - Essex County
      - General, 1942. (Box 37, Folder 12)
      - Civilian Mobilization, 1942. (Box 37, Folder 13)
      - Civilian Protection, 1942. (Box 37, Folder 14)
    - Fairfax County
      - General, 1942. (Box 37, Folder 15)
      - Civilian Mobilization, 1942. (Box 37, Folder 16)
      - Civilian Protection, 1942. (Box 37, Folder 17)
    - Farmville
      - General, 1942. (Box 38, Folder 1)
      - Civilian Mobilization, 1942. (Box 38, Folder 2)
      - Civilian Protection, 1942. (Box 38, Folder 3)
    - Fauquier County
      - General, 1942. (Box 38, Folder 4)
      - Civilian Mobilization, 1942. (Box 38, Folder 5)
      - Civilian Protection, 1942. (Box 38, Folder 6)
    - Floyd County
      - General, 1942. (Box 38, Folder 7)
      - Civilian Mobilization, 1942. (Box 38, Folder 8)
      - Civilian Protection, 1942. (Box 38, Folder 9)
    - Fluvanna County
      - General, 1942. (Box 38, Folder 10)
      - Civilian Mobilization, 1942. (Box 38, Folder 11)
      - Civilian Protection, 1942. (Box 38, Folder 12)
    - Franklin (town of)
      - General, 1942. (Box 38, Folder 13)
      - Civilian Mobilization, 1942. (Box 38, Folder 14)
      - Civilian Protection, 1942. (Box 38, Folder 15)
    - Franklin County
      - General, 1942. (Box 38, Folder 16)
      - Civilian Mobilization, 1942. (Box 38, Folder 17)
      - Civilian Protection, 1942. (Box 38, Folder 18)
    - Frederick County
      - General, 1942. (Box 38, Folder 19)
    - Fredericksburg
      - General, 1942. (Box 39, Folder 1)
      - Civilian Mobilization, 1942. (Box 39, Folder 2)
      - Civilian Protection, 1942. (Box 39, Folder 3)
    - Fries (town of)
      - General, 1942. (Box 39, Folder 4)
    - Galax (town of)
      - General, 1942. (Box 39, Folder 5)
      - Civilian Mobilization, 1942. (Box 39, Folder 6)
      - Civilian Protection, 1942. (Box 39, Folder 7)
    - Giles County
      - General, 1942. (Box 39, Folder 8)
      - Civilian Mobilization, 1942. (Box 39, Folder 9)
      - Civilian Protection, 1942. (Box 39, Folder 10)
    - Gloucester County
      - General, 1942. (Box 39, Folder 11)
      - Civilian Mobilization, 1942. (Box 39, Folder 12)
      - Civilian Protection, 1942. (Box 39, Folder 13)
    - Goochland County
      - General, 1942. (Box 39, Folder 14)
      - Civilian Mobilization, 1942. (Box 39, Folder 15)
      - Civilian Protection, 1942. (Box 39, Folder 16)
    - Grayson County
      - General, 1942. (Box 39, Folder 17)
    - Greene County
      - General, 1942. (Box 39, Folder 18)
    - Greensville County
      - General, 1942. (Box 40, Folder 1)
      - Civilian Mobilization, 1942. (Box 40, Folder 2)
      - Civilian Protection, 1942. (Box 40, Folder 3)
    - Halifax County
      - General, 1942. (Box 40, Folder 4)
      - Civilian Mobilization, 1942. (Box 40, Folder 5)
      - Civilian Protection, 1942. (Box 40, Folder 6)
    - Hanover County
      - General, 1942. (Box 40, Folder 7)
      - Civilian Mobilization, 1942. (Box 40, Folder 8)
      - Civilian Protection, 1942. (Box 40, Folder 9)
    - Harrisonburg
      - General, 1942. (Box 40, Folder 10)
      - Civilian Mobilization, 1942. (Box 40, Folder 11)
      - Civilian Protection, 1942. (Box 40, Folder 12)
    - Henrico County
      - General, 1942. (Box 40, Folder 13)
      - Civilian Mobilization, 1942. (Box 40, Folder 14)
      - Civilian Protection, 1942. (Box 40, Folder 15)
    - Henry County
      - General, 1942. (Box 40, Folder 16)
      - Civilian Mobilization, 1942. (Box 40, Folder 17)
      - Civilian Protection, 1942. (Box 40, Folder 18)
    - Highland County
      - General, 1942. (Box 41, Folder 1)
      - Civilian Mobilization, 1942. (Box 41, Folder 2)
      - Civilian Protection, 1942. (Box 41, Folder 3)
    - Hopewell (town of)
      - General, 1942. (Box 41, Folder 4)
      - Civilian Mobilization, 1942. (Box 41, Folder 5)
      - Civilian Protection, 1942. (Box 41, Folder 6)
      - Civilian Protection - Federal equipment, 1942. (Box 41, Folder 7)
    - Isle of Wight County
      - General, 1942. (Box 41, Folder 8)
      - Civilian Mobilization, 1942. (Box 41, Folder 9)
      - Civilian Protection, 1942. (Box 41, Folder 10)
    - James City County
      - General, 1942. (Box 41, Folder 11)
      - Civilian Mobilization, 1942. (Box 41, Folder 12)
    - King and Queen County
      - General, 1942. (Box 41, Folder 13)
      - Civilian Mobilization, 1942. (Box 41, Folder 14)
      - Civilian Protection, 1942. (Box 41, Folder 15)
    - King George County
      - General, 1942. (Box 41, Folder 16)
      - Civilian Mobilization, 1942. (Box 41, Folder 17)
      - Civilian Protection, 1942. (Box 41, Folder 18)
    - King William County
      - General, 1942. (Box 41, Folder 19)
      - Civilian Mobilization, 1942. (Box 41, Folder 20)
      - Civilian Protection, 1942. (Box 41, Folder 21)
    - Lancaster County
      - General - Reports, 1942. (Box 41, Folder 22)
      - General, 1942. (Box 42, Folder 1)
      - Civilian Mobilization, 1942. (Box 42, Folder 2)
      - Civilian Protection, 1942. (Box 42, Folder 3)
    - Lee County
      - General, 1942. (Box 42, Folder 4)
      - Civilian Mobilization, 1942. (Box 42, Folder 5)
      - Civilian Protection, 1942. (Box 42, Folder 6)
    - Lexington (town of)
      - General, 1942. (Box 42, Folder 7)
      - Civilian Mobilization, 1942. (Box 42, Folder 8)
      - Civilian Protection, 1942. (Box 42, Folder 9)
    - Loudoun County
      - General, 1942. (Box 42, Folder 10)
      - Civilian Mobilization, 1942. (Box 42, Folder 11)
      - Civilian Protection, 1942. (Box 42, Folder 12)
    - Louisa County
      - General, 1942. (Box 42, Folder 13)
      - Civilian Mobilization, 1942. (Box 42, Folder 14)
      - Civilian Protection, 1942. (Box 42, Folder 15)
    - Lunenburg County
      - General, 1942. (Box 42, Folder 16)
      - Civilian Mobilization, 1942. (Box 42, Folder 17)
      - Civilian Protection, 1942. (Box 42, Folder 18)
    - Luray (town of)
      - General, 1942. (Box 42, Folder 19)
      - Civilian Mobilization, 1942. (Box 42, Folder 20)
    - Lynchburg
      - General, 1942. (Box 43, Folder 1)
      - General - Insignia, 1942. (Box 43, Folder 2)
      - General - Negro activities, 1942. (Box 43, Folder 3)
      - General - Publications, 1942. (Box 43, Folder 4)
      - Civilian Mobilization, 1942. (Box 43, Folder 5)
      - Civilian Protection, 1942. (Box 43, Folder 6)
      - Civilian Protection - Blackouts, 1942. (Box 43, Folder 7)
    - Madison County
      - General, 1942. (Box 43, Folder 8)
      - Civilian Mobilization, 1942. (Box 43, Folder 9)
      - Civilian Protection, 1942. (Box 43, Folder 10)
    - Martinsville County
      - General, 1942. (Box 43, Folder 11)
      - Civilian Mobilization, 1942. (Box 43, Folder 12)
      - Civilian Protection, 1942. (Box 43, Folder 13)
    - Mathews County
      - General, 1942. (Box 44, Folder 1)
      - Civilian Mobilization, 1942. (Box 44, Folder 2)
      - Civilian Protection, 1942. (Box 44, Folder 3)
    - Mecklenburg County
      - General, 1942. (Box 44, Folder 4)
      - Civilian Mobilization, 1942. (Box 44, Folder 5)
      - Civilian Protection, 1942. (Box 44, Folder 6)
    - Middlesex County
      - General, 1942. (Box 44, Folder 7)
      - Civilian Mobilization, 1942. (Box 44, Folder 8)
      - Civilian Protection, 1942. (Box 44, Folder 9)
    - Millboro (town of)
      - General, 1942. (Box 44, Folder 10)
    - Montgomery County
      - General, 1942. (Box 44, Folder 11)
    - Nansemond County
      - General, 1942. (Box 44, Folder 12)
      - Civilian Mobilization, 1942. (Box 44, Folder 13)
      - Civilian Protection, 1942. (Box 44, Folder 14)
    - Nelson County
      - General, 1942. (Box 44, Folder 15)
      - Civilian Mobilization, 1942. (Box 44, Folder 16)
      - Civilian Protection, 1942. (Box 44, Folder 17)
    - New Kent County
      - General, 1942. (Box 45, Folder 1)
      - Civilian Mobilization, 1942. (Box 45, Folder 2)
      - Civilian Protection, 1942. (Box 45, Folder 3)
    - Newport News
      - General, 1942. (Box 45, Folder 4)
      - General - Insignia, 1942. (Box 45, Folder 5)
      - General - Publications, 1942. (Box 45, Folder 6)
      - Civilian Mobilization, 1942. (Box 45, Folder 7)
      - Civilian Protection, 1942. (Box 45, Folder 8)
      - Civilian Protection - Blackouts, 1942. (Box 45, Folder 9)
      - Civilian Protection - Federal equipment, 1942. (Box 45, Folder 10)
    - Norfolk County
      - General, 1942. (Box 45, Folder 11)
      - Civilian Mobilization, 1942. (Box 45, Folder 12)
      - Civilian Protection, 1942. (Box 45, Folder 13)
    - Norfolk
      - General, 1942. (Box 46, Folder 1)
      - General - Negro activities, 1942. (Box 46, Folder 2)
      - General - Publications, 1942. (Box 46, Folder 3)
      - Civilian Mobilization, 1942. (Box 46, Folder 4)
      - Civilian Protection, 1942. (Box 46, Folder 5)
      - Civilian Protection - Blackouts, 1942. (Box 46, Folder 6)
      - Civilian Protection - Bomb reconnaissance, 1942. (Box 46, Folder 7)
      - Civilian Protection - Federal equipment, 1942. (Box 46, Folder 8)
    - North Tazewell (town of)
      - General, 1942. (Box 47, Folder 1)
    - Northampton County
      - General, 1942. (Box 47, Folder 2)
      - Civilian Mobilization, 1942. (Box 47, Folder 3)
      - Civilian Protection, 1942. (Box 47, Folder 4)
    - Northumberland County
      - General, 1942. (Box 47, Folder 5)
      - Civilian Mobilization, 1942. (Box 47, Folder 6)
      - Civilian Protection, 1942. (Box 47, Folder 7)
    - Nottoway County
      - General, 1942. (Box 47, Folder 8)
      - Civilian Mobilization, 1942. (Box 47, Folder 9)
      - Civilian Protection, 1942. (Box 47, Folder 10)
    - Orange County
      - General, 1942. (Box 47, Folder 11)
      - Civilian Mobilization, 1942. (Box 47, Folder 12)
      - Civilian Protection, 1942. (Box 47, Folder 13)
    - Page County
      - General, 1942. (Box 47, Folder 14)
    - Pamplin (town of)
      - General, 1942. (Box 47, Folder 15)
    - Patrick County
      - General, 1942. (Box 48, Folder 1)
      - Civilian Mobilization, 1942. (Box 48, Folder 2)
      - Civilian Protection, 1942. (Box 48, Folder 3)
    - Petersburg
      - General, 1942. (Box 48, Folder 4)
      - Civilian Mobilization, 1942. (Box 48, Folder 5)
      - Civilian Protection, 1942. (Box 48, Folder 6)
    - Pittsylvania County